The classic tale as you've never seen.
Dracula: The Original Living Vampire is a horror, fantasy,
thriller film directed by Maximilian Elfeldt.
Detective Amelia Van Helsing is on the desperate hunt for the killer
responsible for a string of grisly murders targeting young women.
Matters only worsen when all evidence leads to the
seemingly untouchable Count Dracula.
And when Van Helsing’s girlfriend vanishes, she is forced to question the very
existence of monsters in a final showdown with the enigmatic count.
Dr. Jack Seward, played by Michael Ironside.
Count Dracula, played by Jake Herbert.
Amelia Van Helsing, played by Christine Prouty.
Mina Murray, played by India Lillie Davies.
Jonathan Harker, played by Ryan Woodcock.
Lucy Westenra, played by Ana Ilic.
This is a list of vampire films.
The film explores themes of vampire, mockbuster, dracula.
The tone is dark and intense.